Lin Hua, you're back.
Sir,
what happened to the dog?
It ate rat poison and died today.
I just buried it,
but the rain washed it out.
I need to dig this pit a bit deeper.
I was wrong! I was wrong!
Give back my shipyard!
Give back my son!
Mr. Ma! Mr. Ma!
Mr. Ma, this won't do.
You'd get him killed, Mr. Ma.
Give back my shipyard!
Give back my son!
S-spare my life!
Mr. Ma.
Make sure to investigate
the cause of this explosion
thoroughly.
The cargo is overdue.
Notify...
the partner company.
Okay.
Here, Mr. Ma. Watch your step.
Thank you, everyone.
Let's go down first.
I'll turn myself in.
If anyone should
turn themselves in, it's me.
You're just a victim.
Whether the police find out or not,
Ma Kai's death
has nothing to do with you.
We can't hide it.
We can't.
Let's go.
Xia Gang killed so many people.
How dare he come here?
It's all Xia Gang's fault.
You died so unjustly.
Mr. Ma,
except for you,
the other twelve victims' families
have all signed.
The reason no one
is making a scene right now
is that you're also a victim's family.
So...
Have they found the cause?
The police are still investigating
the cause of the explosion.
Tell Manager Qiu
to appease the victims' families.
Make sure there's no trouble.
Okay.
I'll take my leave now.
You should go back.
I want to be alone for a while.
Let me stay with you.
Alright, you go back and rest first.
I'll come get you for dinner.
Don't bother.
Lu, did you smell that?
What is that smell?
It smells like something burning.
Xia Xue!
Xue!
What's wrong?
What is that smell?
Lu Ming! Xue!
Xia Xue!
Liu!
Xia's house is on fire.
Hurry!
Xia Xue!
Xia Xue! Xia Xue.
Fire! Help!
Fire!
Hurry!
Come put out the fire!
Hello, Xia Xue.
Come on, let's go play at the beach.
Xia Xue, here's a gift for you.
What do you think
we'll be like in ten years?
Ten years from now?
I think I'll be pretty busy by then.
But don't worry,
I'll come home on time every night.
On weekends, I'll take you out to eat,
go shopping, and watch movies.
And every year,
we'll find time to travel,
to all the places you want to visit.
All the places.
Xia Xue!
I will love you all my life!
I accept that!
What's on your mind?
Where's my motorcycle?
What's wrong with swapping
that motorcycle for a sports car?
You don't know anything.
This car is the only one
in the entire city.
If I drive it, I'll definitely get caught.
Then,
find a dealer
and sell it as a smuggled car.
This car
must be worth a lot of money.
That could work.
But I just don't get it.
My motorcycle is missing,
so Ma Kai must have taken it.
But how did he end up
dead at the shipyard?
Who cares where he died?
This car is ours now anyway.
What do you mean "ours"?
It's mine.
Don't tell anyone about the car.
No smoking in the car.
Dude,
do you buy smuggled cars?
Yes.
I buy anything with wheels.
Which one?
It's not here.
This kind of car is hard to handle.
You have to let me see the car.
Come with me.
Okay.
What are you doing?
You,
come with us.
Who are you?
Mr. Ma
invites you for tea.
M-Mr. Ma?
Sir,
you wanted to see me?
Where are the car keys?
How have you been?
The car keys.
What car keys?
Thank you, Mr. Ma.
Sir,
you mean Kai's car?
I didn't know which car you meant.
Here you are.
Wait—
Sir!
Kai... Kai is not dead.
What do you mean?
Kai wasn't at the explosion site that day.
Kai,
what took you so long?
What's wrong?
You look out of it.
I didn't sleep well.
Check my car for me later.
What happened to it?
I hit a rabbit on the way here.
Wash it.
and check the wheel balance or something.
You got it.
Don't smoke in my car.
Of course not.
Kai,
don't forget the workshop's
safety inspection today.
Screw that.
I'll sit for a bit, then go back to sleep.
Wait,
the city is cracking down on this.
Director Qiu takes it seriously.
Just go sign in and leave.
Did I not sleep well,
or did you?
Do you think I'm afraid of him?
I'm afraid he'll snitch to your father.
We just got out of the police station.
If we piss off the old man,
we won't be able to go out and have fun.
Give me the motorcycle keys.
Here.
Ride slowly.
Yeah.
The day of the explosion,
Kai asked me to fix his car.
He rode my motorcycle to the factory.
He said he just wanted to clock in
and then go home to sleep.
Then the accident happened at the factory.
I went to the site
to look for my motorcycle.
I looked everywhere but couldn't find it.
I figure,
either Kai left before the explosion,
or he never went to the factory at all.
Anyway, he wasn't at the explosion site.
Ma Kai is dead.
And you were looking for a motorcycle?
I went to find Kai and look for
my motorcycle while I was at it.
If we find the motorcycle,
we will definitely find Kai.
Why didn't you say this earlier?
I wouldn't dare
talk about something this big.
It's not that you wouldn't dare.
You're hoping Ma Kai is dead.
You just want that car.
Sir, I really didn't mean that.
I really... I wouldn't dare think that.
Sir,
please give me a chance.
I can definitely find Kai.
Fine. I'll give you a chance.
If Ma Kai is really still alive,
the car is yours.
Hello?
It's Ma Derong. Run a plate for me.
We received a report.
The motorcycle of Ma Kai,
the victim of the shipyard explosion,
is missing.
The license plate number is Ping E57685.
Ma Kai's family suspects
he's still alive.
Surveillance shows that
the motorcycle's last known location
was halfway up Lover's Peak.
I'll let you keep this hand
for a few days.
Thank you, sir.
What's wrong? Why were you looking for me?
A lot of police went to Lover's Peak.
Could they...
Where are you going?
Go wait for me at the plane.
That's right. This is my motorcycle.
Are you sure?
I'm sure.
Start a sweeping search. Move out!
Search!
Hello?
I'm still at Lover's Peak.
The area of Lover's Peak is too large,
so the search is indeed difficult.
Please tell the family that we will
do our best to search.
Report!
We found something here!
Over here.
Here.
Sir, I really didn't lie.
I really believe Kai is fine.
I think he's just afraid you'll find out
he skipped work
on the day of the explosion,
so he went into hiding.
You'd better not
be lying to me about my son.
Sir, I wouldn't dare.
I wouldn't dare.
Sir,
about the car you promised me...
No rush.
Let's find Kai first.
Find Kai first.
I'll get going then.
Have someone keep an eye on that guy.
Lin Hua.
Where exactly did you hide the body?
Don't ask.
It's better if you two don't know.
What do you mean?
Such a big matter,
did you ever discuss it with us?
Discuss what?
This has nothing to do with you two.
I'll take the blame.
How can you take the blame?
If you take the blame,
what about Xia Xue?
Besides, do you have a motive?
You two are college students
with higher education.
Even if you had a conflict with Ma Kai,
would you kill him?
The police just need to ask
around the shipyard,
and they'll know
how Ma Kai usually bullied me.
Who do you think the police will believe?
The police haven't found anything yet.
So Ma Kai...
died at the shipyard.
From now on,
this has nothing to do with you.
Sir,
what happened to the dog?
It ate rat poison and died today.
I just buried it,
but the rain washed it out.
I need to dig the pit deeper.
Go play somewhere else.
Stop messing around.
Believe it or not, I'll smash it.
Give it back to me.
Um, I remember our union
has a DV camera, right?
The one used at last year's party.
Can I borrow it?
Where did you get this?
I found it on the mountain.
This device is mine.
It has my work unit written on it.
Don't play around here.
Go home.
What are you doing? I'll kick you.